<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SeeHisFace</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on SeeHisFace</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 09:37:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Chosen</title><link>/video/the_chosen/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2020 18:51:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>/video/the_chosen/</guid><description>I have just finished watching the first series of The Chosen. Created by Dallas Jenkins, a Christian and a director, writer and film producer, the show is already The highest crowd-funded TV series or film of all time.
The following is from their site and pretty much sums up what it is about:
The Chosen is the first-ever-multi-season TV show about the life of Jesus. Created outside of the Hollywood system, The Chosen allows us to see Him through the eyes of those who knew him.</description></item><item><title>Church History by Dr. James White</title><link>/audio/james_white_church_history/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 07:51:12 +0100</pubDate><guid>/audio/james_white_church_history/</guid><description>www.aomin.org Over the last few weeks I have been listening to an excellent series by Dr. James White from Alpha &amp; Omega Ministries on church history.
69 episodes long, it starts with an introduction as to why church history is important, before giving an overview of the cultural backdrop that the early church found itself in.
The series the moves on the from the church fathers, through the nicene period, the introduction of Islam and the impact that has on the church, then on to the schisms and eventually the reformation, with much else in between.</description></item><item><title>Bible Listening Times</title><link>/audio/2020-05-01-bible-listening-times/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 16:47:01 +0100</pubDate><guid>/audio/2020-05-01-bible-listening-times/</guid><description>Below are the listening times for a particular audio bible I like listening to, the dramatized ESV by Faith Comes By Hearing.
These are the times for the individual books, and for the sections, overall, the whole bible takes just over 80 hours, if listened to at normal speed.
It may be helpful for some people to use for planning listening. Most people read quite a bit faster than they speak, so you could probably half these amount for reading times.</description></item><item><title>Martyn Lloyd Jones Resources</title><link>/audio/martyn-lloyd-jones-resources/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 13:34:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>/audio/martyn-lloyd-jones-resources/</guid><description>&lt;p>I am quite the fan of listening to podcasts and whatnot as I drive around in my van, and I have recently been listening to various Dr. Martyn Lloyd Jones audio sermons. These are quite brilliant, and highly recommended.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The &lt;a href="https://www.mljtrust.org/">MLJ Trust&lt;/a> has made available over 1600 recorded sermons from the great man himself, all for free.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>There is also a mobile app available, which makes the collections easy to navigate, has a built in player, and has a significant introduction to each sermon.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Forbidden Chapter Isaiah 53</title><link>/video/the-forbidden-chapter-isaiah-53/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2020 12:53:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>/video/the-forbidden-chapter-isaiah-53/</guid><description>&lt;p>Today I came across Tree of Life Ministries, and specifically this really great demonstration of using Isaiah 53 in preaching to Jews.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Seemingly most are not even aware of what the chapter says, let alone who it is actually talking about!&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>An Old William Lane Craig Debate</title><link>/video/an-old-william-lane-craig-debate/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2020 21:20:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>/video/an-old-william-lane-craig-debate/</guid><description>&lt;p>Whilst browsing at some William Lane Craig videos yesterday, I came across this debate that I had not seen before.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>It is from 1998 and he is debating with Dr. Keith Parsons, a Professor of Philosophy and a non-believer.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>About</title><link>/about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 09:27:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>/about/</guid><description>Welcome! This site will be an overview and study of books of the bible, along with deeper looks into specific topics.
Along the way there will be reviews and recommendations of books, audio and video, along with anything else I think others would find beneficial.</description></item><item><title>Markdown</title><link>/markdown/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 06:06:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>/markdown/</guid><description>Headings # h1 Heading ## h2 Heading ### h3 Heading #### h4 Heading ##### h5 Heading ###### h6 Heading h1 Heading h2 Heading h3 Heading h4 Heading h5 Heading h6 Heading Horizontal Rules ___ --- *** Typographic replacements Enable typographer option to see result. (c) (C) (r) (R) (tm) (TM) (p) (P) +- test.. test... test..... test?..... test!.... !!!!!! ???? ,, -- --- &amp;#34;Smartypants, double quotes&amp;#34; and &amp;#39;single quotes&amp;#39; Enable typographer option to see result.</description></item></channel></rss>