<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SeeHisFace</title><link>/page/</link><description>Recent content on SeeHisFace</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 09:37:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Terms of Service</title><link>/terms/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2021 21:43:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>/terms/</guid><description>1. Terms By accessing the website at https://seehisface.com, you are agreeing to be bound by these terms of service, all applicable laws and regulations, and agree that you are responsible for compliance with any applicable local laws. If you do not agree with any of these terms, you are prohibited from using or accessing this site. The materials contained in this website are protected by applicable copyright and trademark law.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>/contact/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2021 21:36:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>/contact/</guid><description>Contact me contact domainname.com</description></item><item><title>Cookies Policy</title><link>/cookies-policy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2021 21:36:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>/cookies-policy/</guid><description>This is the Cookie Policy for SeeHisFace, accessible from https://seehisface.com
What Are Cookies
As is common practice with almost all professional websites this site uses cookies, which are tiny files that are downloaded to your computer, to improve your experience. This page describes what information they gather, how we use it and why we sometimes need to store these cookies. We will also share how you can prevent these cookies from being stored however this may downgrade or &amp;lsquo;break&amp;rsquo; certain elements of the sites functionality.</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2021 21:25:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>/privacy-policy/</guid><description>At SeeHisFace, accessible from https://seehisface.com, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by SeeHisFace and how we use it.
If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.
This Privacy Policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in SeeHisFace.</description></item><item><title>Reftagger</title><link>/reftagger/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 20:20:19 +0100</pubDate><guid>/reftagger/</guid><description>John 3:16 John 3.15
John 3:15,16,20
John 3:15,16, 30
This is a reftagger test for John 3:16, testing to see if comma is linked
Test</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>/about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 09:27:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>/about/</guid><description>Welcome! This site will be an overview and study of books of the bible, along with deeper looks into specific topics.
Along the way there will be reviews and recommendations of books, audio and video, along with anything else I think others would find beneficial.
I hope you find something interesting here.</description></item><item><title>Markdown</title><link>/markdown/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 06:06:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>/markdown/</guid><description>Headings # h1 Heading ## h2 Heading ### h3 Heading #### h4 Heading ##### h5 Heading ###### h6 Heading h1 Heading h2 Heading h3 Heading h4 Heading h5 Heading h6 Heading Horizontal Rules ___ --- *** Typographic replacements Enable typographer option to see result. (c) (C) (r) (R) (tm) (TM) (p) (P) +- test.. test... test..... test?..... test!.... !!!!!! ???? ,, -- --- &amp;#34;Smartypants, double quotes&amp;#34; and &amp;#39;single quotes&amp;#39; Enable typographer option to see result.</description></item></channel></rss>